# https://opentdb.com/api_config.php

random_question_data = [
{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"General Knowledge",
"question":"In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.",
"correct_answer":"True",
"incorrect_answers":["False"]},

{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"General Knowledge","question":"This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"French is an official language in Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Francis Bacon died from a fatal case of pneumonia while he was attempting to preserve meat by stuffing a chicken with snow.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The color orange is named after the fruit.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Ping-Pong originated in England","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Lego Group was founded in 1932.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Furby was released in 1998.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"General Knowledge","question":"NCIS stands for &quot;Navy Corps Investigative Service&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Bulls are attracted to the color red.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"There are 86400 seconds in a day.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Pluto is a planet.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Number 16 Bus Shelter&quot; was a child&#039;s name that was approved by the New Zealand government.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr. and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]